RG 067, Architectural and Engineering Drawings
Connecticut State Library
Architectural and engineering drawings
9999-9999
Connecticut State Library
999 cubic feet
RG067
Multiple
Container List
- Series 1. Connecticut Towns
  - Berlin
    - Plan of proposed hospital at Berlin with map of proposed site, undated; 8 sheets (Folder Folder 1)
      - Cover sheet, paper on cloth, 16 x 12.5 in.
      - Floor plans and elevations, paper on cloth, 15 x 19 in.
      - Floor plan, paper on cloth, 10 x 24 in.
      - Floor plan, paper on cloth, 16 x 23.5 in.
      - Floor plan, paper on cloth, 12 x 19 in.
      - Elevation, paper on cloth, 17.5 x 22.5 in.
      - Elevation, paper on cloth, 17.5 x 21 in.
      - Elevation, paper on cloth, 17.5 x 23.5 in.
  - Bloomfield
    - East Branch Library, 1917; Butterfield & Associates, Architects; 27 sheets (Folder Folder 9)
      - Cover sheet, 1917 January 4; paper, 18 x 24 in.
      - Site details, 1917 March 25; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1 foot; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: L3
      - Site details, 1917 March 25; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1 foot; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: L4
      - Abbreviations, legends, drawing list, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Sheet number: A6
      - Room finish schedule, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Sheet number: A7
      - Window schedule and door types, 1917 January 4; paper, 18 x 24 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A8
      - Window details and miscellaneous details, 1917 January 4; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot; 3 inches = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A9
      - Door schedule, 1917 January 4; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Sheet number: A10
      - Vertical details, 1917 April 12; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot; 3 inches = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A11
      - Vertical details, 1917 April 12; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot; 3 inches = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A12
      - Vertical details, 1917 April 12; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot; 3 inches = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A13
      - Vertical details, 1917 April 12; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A14
      - Miscellaneous details, 1917 April 12; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot; 3 inches = 1 foot; .75 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A15
      - Window wall details, 1917 April 12; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 3 inches = 1 foot
        Sheet number: A16
      - General notes, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: S3
      - Typical details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: S4
      - Typical details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: S5
      - Foundation details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.; .75 inch = 1 foot
        Document number: S6
      - Foundation details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.; .75 inch = 1 foot
        Document number: S7
      - Superstructure details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
        Document number: S8
      - Superstructure details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
        Document number: S9
      - Superstructure details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
        Document number: S10
      - Column schedule, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: S11
      - Control and device details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: M2
      - Panelboard schedule and power and telephone riser diagram, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: E2
      - Electrical fixtures and symbol list schedule, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: E3
      - Plumbing details, undated; paper, 18 x 24 in.
        Document number: P3
  - Branford
    - Alterations and additions to Knights of Pythias Hall, undated; Allen & Williams Architects; 10 sheets (Folder Folder 1)
      - Basement plan, paper, 35 x 27.5 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - First floor plan, paper, 35 x 27.5 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Second floor plan, paper, 35 x 27.5 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Front elevation, paper, 20.5 x 30 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Side elevation, paper, 21 x 37 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Side elevation, paper, 21 x 37 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Rear elevation, paper, 20.5 x 30 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Traverse section looking toward gallery, paper, 20.5 x 30 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Traverse section looking toward front, paper, 20.5 x 30 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Longitudinal section, paper, 20.5 x 30 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
  - Derby
    - Sterling Opera House, 1974; Caswell Cook & Associates; 4 sheets (Folder Folder 1)
      - Northeast perspective of Sterling Opera House, 1974 March; paper, 24 x 36 in.
      - Site plan, 1974 May 31; paper, 24 x 36 in.; .05 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: 1
      - Eastern elevation, 1974 May 31; paper, 24 x 36 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
        Sheet number: 2
      - Floor plan, 1974 May 31; paper, 24 x 36 in.
  - Granby
    - Community House, undated; Whiton & McMahon; 1 sheet (Folder Folder 9)
      - Plan of ground floor and main floor, paper, 18.5 x 23 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
  - Greenwich
    - State Armory, undated; Frederick G. C. Smith; 8 sheets (Folder Folder 9)
      - Basement plan, paper, 24 x 18 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - First floor plan, paper, 24 x 18 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - Second floor plan, paper, 24 x 18 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - Roof plan, paper, 24 x 18 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - Front elevation, paper, 18 x 24 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - Side elevation, paper, 18 x 24 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - Side elevation, paper, 18 x 24 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
      - Rear elevation, paper, 18 x 24 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
  - Hartford
    - A comprehensive study for Bushnell Park, State Captiol and Armory grounds, 1944; Olmstead Brothers, Landscape architects; 1 sheet (Folder Folder 6)
      - Master plan, paper, 26 x 43 in.; .02 inch = 1 foot
    - State Capitol plan for bronze tablet, 1911 January 12; W.M.H. Jackson Co.; 1 sheet (Folder Folder 7)
      - Signage and detail section, 1911 January 12; paper, 42.5 x 52 in.; full scale
    - State Library and Supreme Court Building (Folder Folder 7)
      - Site plan for proposed addition, undated; paper, 17.5 x 21.5 in.; Hartford (Conn.). Dept. of Engineering; .02 inch = 1 foot
      - Site plan showing property line between State of Connecticut and Mabel G. Gilman, Trustee, 1957 August; paper, 16 x 22 in.; Petersen & Hoffman, Engineers; .1 inch = 1 foot
      - First story plan, ground story plan, second story plan, circa 1912; paper, photocopy 18 x 11 in.; .125 inch = 1 foot
    - State Library and Supreme Court Building addition, 1965-1966; Standard Structural Steel Co.; 30 sheets (Folder Folder 7)
      - Structural drawing, columns 26, 27, 29, 1965 December 1; paper, 24 x 36 in.
      - Structural drawing, columns 28, 31, 1965 October 7; paper, 24 x 36 in.
      - Structural drawing, columns 30, 25, 1965 October 7; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 3
      - Structural drawing, columns 15, 18, 16, 19, 1965 October 8; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 4
      - Structural drawing, columns 21, 9, 1965 October 11; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 5
      - Structural drawing, columns 22, 10, 1965 October 12; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 6
      - Structural drawing, columns 24, 23, 1965 October 13; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 7
      - Structural drawing, columns 11, 12, 1965 October 16; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 8
      - Structural drawing, columns 13, 7, 1965 October 18; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 9
      - Structural drawing, columns 14, 17, 12, 10, 11, 22, 8, 20, undated; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 136
      - Structural drawing, columns 9, 21, 23, 24, undated; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 137
      - Structural drawing, columns 9, 21, 23, 24, 1966 January 18; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 138
      - Structural drawing, columns 33, 34, 35, 36, 1966 January 18; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 139
      - Structural drawing, columns 33, 34, 35, 36, 1965 October 20; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 140
      - Structural drawing, one truss T1A, 1965 October 20; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 141
      - Structural drawing, 1966 January 31; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 142
      - Structural drawing, one truss T2, 1965 December 30; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 143
      - Structural drawing, 1965 December 29; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 144
      - Structural drawing, one truss T2A, 1965 October 13; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 145
      - Structural drawing, columns 20, 8, 1965 October 20; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 205
      - Structural drawing, columns 17, 14, 1965 October 20; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 206
      - Structural drawing, columns 28, 27, 29, 26, 30, 1965 October 20; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 207
      - Structural drawing, columns 7, 1965 October 20; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: 208
      - Structural drawing, 1965 September 21; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E1
      - Structural drawing, 1965 September 22; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E2
      - Structural drawing, 1965 September 23; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E3
      - Structural drawing, 1965 October 1; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E4
      - Structural drawing, 1965 October 1; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E5
      - Structural drawing, 1965 November 1; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E6
      - Structural drawing, 1965 September 23; paper, 24 x 36 in.
        Sheet number: E7
    - Friends of Hartford. Daniel Wadsworth Barn, 1952; George Dunkelberger; 4 sheets (Folder Folder 6)
      - South elevation and details, paper, 18 x 33 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot; 1.5 inch = 1 foot
      - North elevation, paper, 18 x 33 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - West elevation, paper, 18 x 33 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot
      - Ground floor plan elevation and details, paper, 18 x 33 in.; .25 inch = 1 foot